♪ You know I'm crazy about you, honey...♪
纸牌游戏
The game of poker...
桌上放52张牌
52 cards in a deck,
手里拿7张
seven in a hand.
一亿三千三百万种组合
133 million different possible combinations.
提问 有没有必胜的方法
The question is: can the game be beaten?
你有概率值
You got your probability,
有收益计算
your equity calculations,
你得统计分析
you got statistical analysis...
但考虑到所有情况后 伙计们 你们要懂人的心理
but at the end of the day, folks, you got to know people.
好了 几位好先生 问题来了
So, I ask you fine gentlemen.
扑克是一个技巧类游戏
Is poker a game of skill
还是个投机类游戏
or is it a game of chance?
Elvis 别跟我们扯理论了
Elvis, enough of the game theory.
你到底是跟还是不跟
Are you gonna bet or what?
这样的话
In that case...
我全押上
I'm all in.
没人想试一下我的理论
No one's gonna test my thesis.
大家都只想让你闭嘴
Everybody wants you to shut up.
喔 我会让你们满意的
Well, I aim to please, then.
嗨 我们出去透个气
Hey, let's catch a breath.
快
Come on.
马上就来
I'll be right out.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
这可真滑稽 伙计们
Hilarious, guys.
非常好笑 我不知道你们这么输不起
Very funny. I didn't know you guys were such sore losers.
GA 字幕组
本字幕仅用于学习交流使用 严禁商业用途
翻译：二噁英  包子  栗子是个男生=_=
翻译：Echo  兔子  Lily  草菇
校对：流年  阿珂姑娘  大师兄  师太
总校：流年
时间轴&调整：想吃KFC的栗子
NCIS 新奥尔良
S03E02
你还挺随便的
Made yourself at home.
我们有很多事情要讨论
You and I have a lot to discuss.
我认为你不会介意
I figured you wouldn't mind
我用了你们的会议室
if I used your conference room.
我尽量不让你们感到不快 Pride探员
I'll make this as painless as possible, Agent Pride.
一个安插在国土安全局的间谍渗透进了你们的队伍
A DHS mole infiltrated your team.
司法部只是想让我们确认一下
The DOJ just wants us to make sure
这件事没什么需要担心的
that there's nothing to worry about.
这不是针对谁
It's not personal.
只有你觉得不是针对谁而已
Not for you.
这个嘛
Well...
我不是来玩什么"捉住你了" 之类的游戏
I'm not here to play gotcha.
Pride特别探员
Special Agent Pride,
你的队伍发现证据证明国土安全局特工John Russo
is it true your team found evidence
是一个为Ciudad Natal贩毒集团工作的双面间谍
Homeland Security Agent John Russo was a double agent
这是真的吗
working for the Ciudad Natal Cartel?
是真的
That's correct.
那你能不能告诉我
And can you tell me why you chose
为什么你选择违反程序
to break procedure and neglect
没有立即向Russo的上司或者你自己的上司汇报呢
to report Russo immediately to his superiors or your own?
四个NCIS探员涉及多起事件
Four NCIS agents responsible for multiple...
他们在上边多久了
How long they been up there?
不久
Not long.
听到什么了
What do you hear?
现在的话 只听到你了
Well, right now, just you.
我们发现Russo是个双面间谍
We discover Russo's a double agent,
我们把他拿下了
we bring him down,
现在我们却要被审查了
and now we're the ones under review.
是的 这叫政府机关业务
Yeah, it's called government work.
不管怎样 Pride看起来
Still, looks like Pride is...
-很不开心 -很不开心
- pretty upset. - pretty upset.
他们需要点空间
They need their privacy.
没错 我们还有活要干
Yeah, we got work to do,
比如接听那个电话
like answering that phone call.
你觉得我不该在这里
You don't think that I should be here.
我明白
I get it.
在你看来 你们是英雄
In your estimation, you're heroes
我们应该感激你们 然后这事就过去了
and we should just thank you and move on.
那当然最好
That'd be nice.
以我的角度看来
Look at it from my perspective.
国土安全局高层出了间谍
A mole in Homeland Security at the highest level.
你们城市差点发生一起恐怖袭击
A major attack on your city, barely stopped.
-是我的队伍阻止了他们 -是的
- By my team. - Yes.
没错 正是你队伍里的人出了事
Yes, one of whom was compromised
而尘埃落定以后 这个人又辞职了
and when the dust settled, resigned.
你在怪罪Brody
You're blaming Brody?
陈述事实而已 四个NCIS探员
Stating facts. Four NCIS agents
对海湾沿岸的事故负有责任
responsible for most of the Gulf Coast.
Meredith Brody与一个毒品集团的间谍有亲密关系
Meredith Brody was intimately involved with a cartel spy.
如果不是她 John Russo已经成功了
If it wasn't for her, John Russo would have succeeded.
司法部不容许
And the DOJ is not comfortable
任何微小失误的存在
with such a slim margin of error.
我们在忙呢
In the middle of something!
多重谋杀案
Multiple homicide,
死者包括Creole Queen号上的一名海军军官
including a dead Navy officer on the Creole Queen.
工作在召唤 Isler探员
Work calls, Agent Isler.
不好意思了
Sorry about that.
你还好吗 King
You good, King?
再好不过了
Dandy.
受害者是汽车销售Milton Lewis
Victims are Milton Lewis, car salesman;
承包商Travis Cane
Travis Cane, contractor.
还有海军少校Henry Warbeck
And Lieutenant Commander Henry Warbeck.
Belle Chasse的网络战工程师
Cyber warfare engineer out of Belle Chasse.
都是近距离直接射杀
All shot point-blank, close range.
有目击者吗
Witnesses?
没有 Creole Queen号正在港内翻新
No. The Creole Queen was docked for renovations.
Travis在这里 他监管这个工作
Travis here, he oversaw the work.
根据新奥尔良警察局的说法 Cane浮夸的牌技很出名
According to NOPD, Cane's known for his floating poker game.
根据桌上的筹码和空空的保险柜
And judging from the chips on the table and the empty
我敢说这里曾经有不少现金
strong box, I'd say there was a lot of cash here.
盗窃被抓
Burglary gone wrong?
不 这看起来更像是处决
No, it's more like an execution.
受害者都在桌上被射杀
All the victims were shot here at the table,
没有挣扎的迹象
and there's no sign of them putting up a struggle.
这几个受害者也许没挣扎
Well, these victims might not have struggled...
有人挣扎了
someone else did.
赌桌都被掀翻了
Overturned blackjack table.
天花板上还有子弹孔
Bullet holes in the ceiling.
那是血迹吗
That blood?
这个
And this...
是杀手的帽子吗
Belonged to the killer?
是Elvis Bertrand的帽子
Belongs to Elvis Bertrand.
你知道这个人吗
That name mean something to you?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
Elvis曾是一名海军情报分析员
Elvis was a Navy intelligence analyst.
他几年前跟进过一起间谍案
He consulted on an espionage case a few years back.
为了挖一个间谍网而把自己置身危险之中
Put himself on the line to take out a spy ring.
从那时起我们才相熟
We became close.
他一直是King少数几个密友之一
He's been a handful for King ever since.
那他有没有辜负自己的名声呢
So, does he live up to the name?
酗酒 读博 生存 没错
Hard drinking, gambling, living, yeah.
不太配得上海军制服
Not exactly cut from Navy cloth.
确实 但是在网络战上是个十足的高手
No, but a savant when it came to cyber warfare.
最厉害的那种
One of the best.
我都数不清
I lost count of how many times
Pride把他从牢里保释出来多少回了
Pride's had to bail him out of a rough spot.
是关押多重谋杀犯的牢房吗
Like triple murder rough?
Elvis是个黑客 麻烦精
Elvis is a hacker, troublemaker,
还算半个骗子 但是绝不是杀手
half a con man, but no kind of killer.
好吧 不过这看起来并不乐观啊 King
Well, it doesn't look good, King.
嗨
Hey.
我们去询问目击证人 检查监控录像
We'll canvass witnesses, check surveillance.
我们会找到Elvis的
We'll find Elvis.
看你的表情
Judging from expression,
你今天下午没什么进展
you have not had a productive afternoon.
我们去了Elvis的公寓 最喜欢的酒吧
Went to Elvis's apartment, favorite bar,
第二喜欢的酒吧 任何一个我曾经见到过
second favorite bar, every place I've ever found him
他的地方 没什么发现
in the past-- no luck.
在当今这个时代 他不会那么难找的
Well, he can't be that hard to find, not in this day and age.
全球定位 数字记录
GPS, digital trail.
Elvis太精明又太偏执
Elvis is too smart and too paranoid
不会留下任何痕迹的
to leave any kind of trace.
如果他想玩消失 我们就找不到他
If he wants off the grid, he's gone.
或者他可能是另一个受害者
Or he could be another victim.
我尽量不要让这个想法分散我的注意力
I'm trying not to let that idea distract me.
你的注意力已经被分散了 Dwayne
You're already distracted, Dwayne.
FBI的审查
The FBI review.
没错 与其说审查不如说是一场联合攻击
Yeah. Not so much a review as a coordinated attack.
你一定会圆滑地处理
Well, sure you handled it diplomatically.
我确实是
I did.
直到Isler开始对Merri指指点点
Until Isler started pointing fingers at Merri.
就把她当替罪羊了
Used her as a scapegoat, then?
你怎么处理的
How'd you handle that?
不那么圆滑 那是肯定的
Not diplomatically, that's for sure.
太抱歉了 我很抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
我已经能等多久等多久了
Uh, I waited as long as I could.
我知道你们在进行私人对话
I know you're having a private conversation.
我只是 我必须来拿受害者的个人物品
I just... I got to get the victim's personal effects.
没关系 Sebastian
It's okay, Sebastian.
那太好了 因为我实在太想知道了
Okay, great, 'cause, look, I'm dying to know:
牵扯进这个案子的是那个Elvis Bertrand吗
is the Elvis Bertrand involved in this case?
-你认识他 -我 我倒是希望能认识他
- You know him? - Well, I-I wish.
他就像 他就像是黑客之星
He's like the... he's like the hacker of the people.
他黑进公司内网
He breaks into corporate computer networks,
然后公布所有见不得人的交易
then he releases all their dirty laundry.
他简直是我心目中的英雄
He's a personal hero.
有那样的特长会树敌很多 Sebastian
Made a lot of enemies pulling those stunts, Sebastian,
包括司法部门
including the Justice Department.
为了免除牢狱之灾
Got himself banned from using the Internet
他被禁止使用网络 但他无视了这个禁令
instead of jail time... a ban he ignored.
这声音是从物证中来的
That's coming from the evidence.
Warbeck少校的手机
Commander Warbeck's phone.
嘿 给我个手套
Hey, give me a glove.
Elvis
Elvis?
这正是我喜欢你的地方 Dwayne 你接一个
That's what I love about you, Dwayne; you answer
死人的电话 但你就是知道是我打来的
a dead man's phone, and somehow you know it's me calling.
跟他说我是他的粉丝
Tell him I'm a fan.
到底发生了什么
What the hell is going on?
我很想要坐下来边喝秋葵浓汤边和你说
Well, I'd love to sit and chat over a bowl of gumbo,
但在他们追踪到我的手机之前
but I got about 30 seconds
我只有三十秒
before they can track the phone I'm on.
他们是谁 Elvis
Who's they, Elvis?
呃 政府
Uh, the government,
私人调查员 那些人 还有你 据我所知
private sector, “the Man,” you, for all I know.
现在我们只剩20秒了
Now we got 20 seconds.
你听上去太偏执了
You're sounding paranoid.
如果是这些人在追踪我 这就不算偏执
Well, you're not paranoid if they are actually after you,
而且我的确是刚刚死里逃生
and I did barely survive a massacre.
我还有10秒钟 Dwayne
I got ten seconds, Dwayne.
我要你在四小时内与我见面 你一个人来
I need you to meet me in four hours... alone.
好
Okay.
把地址给我
Give me an address.
♪ You don't own me ♪
♪ I'm not just one of your many toys ♪
♪ Don't say I can't go with other boys ♪
♪ Don't tell me what to do ♪
♪ And don't tell me what to say ♪
♪ Please, when I go out with you ♪
♪ Don't put me on display... ♪
我还指望你把我的帽子带来呢
I was hoping you brought my hat,
因为 我跟你讲 我不喜欢我头上这玩意
'cause I tell you, this thing on my head ain't working.
那顶帽子是三重谋杀的物证
Hat's evidence in a triple murder.
是 不过我可没杀人
Yeah, well, I didn't kill nobody.
如果是这样
Sure.
♪ You don't own me... ♪
那想知道 你带着把枪做什么
Just kind of wondering what you're doing with a gun.
我今天过得很不好
Well, I had a bad day.
需要一点保护
Need a little protection.
我现在在这了
Well, I'm here now...
所以把枪递给我吧
so hand it over.
你要知道 新闻上把扑克室发生的事
You know, the news reports are calling what happened
叫做抢劫
in the poker room a robbery.
说的都是一堆废话
It's a bunch of crap.
那是一场暗杀
It was an assassination.
而我想知道事情的全部经过
And I want to hear all about it.
但首先把枪给我 Elvis
But first the gun, Elvis.
你以为我会开枪打你么
You think I would ever shoot you?!
我以为你会把枪给我
I think you're gonna give me the gun,
然后我们会回NCIS
and when we go back to NCIS,
我给你准备秋葵浓汤 你告诉我发生了什么
I'm gonna get you some gumbo, you'll tell me what happened.
♪ The way I want ♪
♪ To say and do whatever I please... ♪
你觉得怎么样 Elvis
What's it gonna be Elvis？
我以为你是自己来的
I thought you said you were coming alone.
我是
I did.
那这些人是谁
Well, who are those guys?!
Elvis Bertrand FBI 把手举起来
Elvis Bertrand, FBI. Hands where I can see them.
特别探员Gregorio
Special Agent Gregorio.
Isler让你跟着我
Isler have you follow me?
不 我们是来带回谋杀嫌疑犯的
No. Here to take in a murder suspect.
嘿 我哪也不去
Hey, I'm not going anywhere.
把你拷回去还是推回去 我不在乎
In cuffs or a gurney, doesn't matter.
但我在乎
Well, matters to me.
-枪 -Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
- Gun. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-让开 -冷静
- Out of the way. - Calm down.
让开
Out of the way!
所有人冷静
Everybody calm down.
让开 特别探员Pride
Out of the way, Special Agent Pride!
抱歉 Dwayne 我谁都不相信
Sorry, Dwayne. You can't trust nobody.
Elvis Elvis
Elvis! Elvis!
Elvis
Elvis?
Elvis!
老兄 他跑了
Dude, he's gone.
我猜Elvis已经离开这栋楼了
I guess Elvis has left the building.
和我走走
Take a walk.
我一会给你回电话
I'll call you back.
你的酒友能设法逃脱
Your drinking buddy somehow managed to elude
这么多联邦探员
a dozen federal agents.
因为你把他吓走了
'Cause you scared him off.
难道我要在以谋杀罪逮捕他之前
Was I supposed to say “pretty please”
说几句求求你么
when I arrested him for murder?
那就是NOLA的做事方法吗
Is that the NOLA way?
Elvis有很多身份 但不是杀人犯
Elvis is many things; murderer is not one.
他是个犯下众多联邦案件的重罪犯
He's a felon convicted of a dozen federal crimes,
包括黑客行为
including hacking.
Elvis和我的小组的审查一点关系都没有
Elvis has nothing to do with my team's review.
你到底在这干什么
Why the hell are you even here?
这镇子比我记忆中还小
Smaller town than I remember.
人们总会遇到的
People run into each other.
尤其是当他们调查的是同一个案子时
Especially when they're investigating the same case.
这我还真不知道
Didn't realize we were.
哦 所以你也不是什么都知道
Oh, so you don't know everything.
你想再来一个惊喜吗
You want another surprise?
认识他吗
Recognize him?
我应该认识吗
Should I?
我还以为你认识这镇上的每个人呢
Figured you knew everyone in this town.
Elvis的后备箱里有个死人
Dead man in Elvis's trunk.
你再说一遍他不是个杀人犯
Tell me again he's not a murderer.
Warbeck少校是海军的计算机工程师
Commander Warbeck was a Navy computer engineer.
Elvis是前海军情报人员
Elvis is former Navy Intelligence.
所以这是NCIS的事儿 不是你的
That's NCIS's stake here. Not seeing yours.
Warbeck曾参与过国防部和司法部的一项安防工程
Warbeck worked a security project for DoD and Justice.
这事我还是第一次听说
First time hearing about it.
你对水下光纤电缆了解多少
What do you know about underwater fiber-optic cables?
我也一无所知
I know squat, too.
只知道他们传输着各种各样的敏感数据
Except they carry all kinds of sensitive data.
Warbeck帮助保护数据
Warbeck helped secure the data,
Natal Cartel想窃取数据
Natal Cartel wanted to steal it.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
IDI投资银行巴西分行
IDI Investment Bank in Brazil
掌握了Ciudad Natal千万资产
handles hundreds of millions of Ciudad Natal's money.
我们一直在监视光缆上的秘密交易
We've been monitoring the transactions on the cables.
结果发现 不只我们一家在监视
Turns out, we're not the only ones.
你认为Natal Cartel黑进了光缆吗
You think the Natal Cartel is hacking these cables?
你正因为贩毒集团双重间谍一事
You're under review regarding
而被调查
a cartel double agent.
你得退出 让机动部队来处理这事
You need to step off and let the cavalry handle it.
我手上有一名死亡的海军军官
I got a dead Navy officer.
你的手下是首要嫌疑目标
Your buddy's the prime suspect.
再提醒一次 你在接受审查
Again, you're under review.
是啊 但没那么容易
Yeah. Not that easy.
在你或者你那"机动部队"误杀Elvis之前
I'm gonna go find Elvis before you or your “cavalry”
我会找到他
put a bullet in him by mistake.
说的对
Fair enough.
Loretta女士
Miss Loretta.
我想要最近一位受害者的尸检结果
Hoping to get autopsy results on our latest victims.
不只你想要
You're not alone.
Isler和FBI
Isler and the FBI
几分钟前拿着许可证
came a few minutes ago with a warrant,
把受害者
and they're taking the victims
和我的验尸结果一起带回了他们的实验室
and my results back to their crime lab.
Elvis车里那个无名氏也带走了吗
Even the John Doe from Elvis's car?
他们让我停手之前
I barely had time to photograph the body
我都来不及给尸体拍照
before they told me to cease and desist.
我不喜欢半途而废
I hate leaving something undone.
吱
Psst.
过来
Come over here!
我有东西给你们
I have something for you.
但我不想他们知道
But I don't want them to know,
让我们低调一些 好吗
so let's be inconspicuous, okay?
大家表现的自然点儿
Everyone just act normal.
Sebastian 你现在比刚才
Sebastian, you couldn't look more conspicuous
还要显眼
than you do right now.
你查到了什么 老兄
What you got, my brother?
我在Warbeck少校的个人物品里找到了这个
I found it in Commander Warbeck's personal effects.
像是门卡 那种
Looks like a key card that you find in a...
恩
Mm...
看上去是不是很像办公室或者酒店里用的
Looks like a common key card
很普通的门卡 不是的
that you'd use in any office or hotel, right? Wrong.
我试着分析了一下芯片
Tried to analyze the chip.
它的加密算法的安全标准仅次于
Encryption is, like, next-level secure,
国家安全局
only available to NSA,
中情局
CIA...
真的 所有带A的缩写词
Really, any of the “A” acronyms.
那就说得通了
Well, that makes sense.
Warbeck曾为水下光缆
Warbeck was working a cyber security project
做过网络安防工程
on underwater fiber optics.
嘿 你要是能找出这个卡来自哪里
Hey, you figure out where that key card comes from,
你就能给我们提供Warbeck被害的线索了
you can give us the lead on why Warbeck was killed.
说起来容易 做起来难 但是Patton和我
Easier said than done, but Patton and I
潜心研究 破译了这玩意儿
got down and dirty, and we decrypted this bad boy.
结果发现 这个卡属于某个叫Certel的公司
Turns out, it belongs to some company
这公司和政府有合约
called Certel-- contracts with the government.
我不清楚 Pride正往那里赶
I don't know-- Pride's on his way there right now.
不 我的理解是
No, it's my understanding
我们不参与这件案子
that we aren't on this case.
或者我们可以把FBI的命令当耳旁风
Or are we taking the FBI order as optional?
Pride肯定当耳旁风了 我们得帮他
Well, Pride sure is, and we got his back.
[注：“Pig Latin” 密语]
哦 后面来人了
Oh, ixnay on the ack-bay.
特别探员Lasalle和Percy
Special Agents Lasalle and Percy.
你们现在有空吧
Got some free time on your hands?
不妨回FBI 把谈话结束
Why not come back to the FBI, get your interviews over with?
我以为FBI在处理
Thought FBI was handling
Warbeck少校谋杀案 Pride探员
Commander Warbeck's murder, Agent Pride.
这是联合调查
Call it a joint investigation.
我的人发现了少校的门卡
My team found the commander's key card,
追踪到了这儿 Certel公司
traced it here to Certel.
你们做网络安全
You do cyber security.
我们维护南半球
We secure the integrity of underwater
水下光纤电缆的整体性
fiber-optic cables across the Southern Hemisphere.
Warbeck少校负责什么
And Commander Warbeck's role?
Henry是来做威胁评估的国防部联络员
Henry was DoD liaison for Threat Assessment.
是我的部门
That's my division.
不好意思 让我再试一次
Uh, sorry, let me just try this again.
10位数密码
Ten-number key code.
每天都换
Changed on a daily basis.
很重视安保工作啊
Take your security seriously, huh?
我们的职责嘛
It's our business.
额
Uh...
我们最近都有点紧张
we've all been a little on edge lately.
你和Warbeck少校工作关系很好吗
You and Commander Warbeck work closely together?
我们共同管理这个部门两年了
We oversaw the division for two years.
多次奋战到深夜
A lot of late nights.
Warbeck少校遇害
Commander Warbeck's murder
或许和他在这儿的工作有关
may have been related to his work here.
他说的没错
Then he was right.
我们在这些服务器上监视着百万字节的数据
We monitor millions of terabytes of data on these servers.
公司的一举一动
Everything from corporate correspondence
还有敏感的政府谈话
to sensitive government communication.
Henry觉得他发现了一个监视软件
Henry thought he found a sniffer.
什么
A what?
在光缆上有一个虚拟窃听器
It's a virtual bug on the cable.
用于窃听数据
Used to steal data.
他没有上报过关于黑客的事
He never reported a hack.
做这个事情的人很厉害
Whoever placed it was good.
Henry需要确认
Henry needed confirmation,
所以他去找了他觉得他能信任的人
so he went to the one person he thought he could trust,
Elvis Bertrand
Elvis Bertrand.
他们一起服役过
They served together.
他是Henry见过的最厉害的黑客
He was the best hacker Henry knew.
有可能
It's possible
是有人背叛了Certel公司
whoever breached Certel
意识到Warbeck少校正在查这事
realized what Commander Warbeck was onto.
为此便杀害了他
Killed him for it.
你对那个黑客知道多少
Do you know anything about the hacker?
什么都不知道
Nothing.
你得和Elvis谈谈
You need to talk to Elvis.
他是唯一一个能够搞清楚这个漏洞的人
He's the only other person who can figure out this breach.
Patton 请告诉我你已经追查到了Elvis
Patton, please tell me you've tracked down Elvis.
你哥们Elvis很牛掰
Oh, your buddy Elvis is scary good.
他开机打几个简短的电话
He turns his phone on long enough
然后关机
to make short calls, and then he powers it down.
所以 没发现
So, no luck.
嘿 我也很不错
Hey, I'm scary good, too.
我不得不跑出来 移动追查
I had to hit the streets and go mobile.
我不能告诉你他手机现在在哪儿
I can't tell you where his phone is,
但我能告诉你它曾经在哪儿
but I can tell you where it was.
自从谋杀案开始 Elvis就从城市公园的某处
Ever since the murders, Elvis has been making several calls
打了几通电话
from somewhere in City Park.
Elvis一直对旋转木马情有独钟
Elvis always had a soft spot for the flying horses.
叫Sonja和Lasalle在那儿和我汇合
Have Sonja and Lasalle meet me there.
哦 我以为你知道呢 LaSalle和Sonja脱不了身
Oh, I thought you knew. Lasalle and Sonja's tied up.
就在我们说话的同时 FBI在审讯他们呢
The FBI is interviewing them as we speak.
我现在算是知道灌肠的感觉是什么样子的了
Guess I know what a high colonic feels like now.
他们问你Merri的事情了吗
They ask you about Merri?
对 她和Russo的关系
Yeah, and her relationship with Russo.
持续了多久 关系有多亲密
How long it was, how intense.
我是否信任她 废话 我当然信任她
Did I trust her? Yeah, I trust her.
对 比这些蠢货们更值得新任
Yeah, more than these “feeb” jokers.
他们也问了我King的事情
They asked me about King, too.
他有破坏协议的习惯吗
Did he make it a habit of breaking protocol?
听着 Isler将阻止恐怖袭击
Look, Isler's gonna make stopping a terrorist attack
变成实施恐怖袭击  把我们都坑惨了
into an actionable offense, hanging us all out to dry.
我想知道
I want to know.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
那边有情况
There's something going on over there.
我没听到太多
I couldn't catch a lot of it.
很多低声的对话 但
A lot of whispered conversation, but...
我觉得他们发现了Elvis
I think they got a line on Elvis.
那让我们查个明白
Well, let's find out.
你要跟踪她吗
You want to follow her?
你知道这会给我们带来多大的麻烦吗
You know how much trouble that's gonna get us in?
我们已经麻烦缠身了
We're already in trouble.
到处都没有Elvis的消息
No sign of Elvis anywhere.
我能告诉你的就是 你要找的人昨天
All I can tell you is your boy was clocking
在这里用了几小时做了些很重要的事
some serious hours around here yesterday.
据我目前所知 他现在可能在古巴
Far as I know, he can be in Cuba by now.
Patton
Patton?
Patton 你能听到吗
Patton, you there?
不 不 是我 Fidel Castro 我黑进了你们的通话
No, no, it's me, Fidel Castro, hacking in.
我断掉了Patton的线路
I disconnected Patton.
虽然你的人竟能追踪到我 令我印象深刻
Although I am impressed that you boys actually tracked me down.
我们该好好谈谈了
We got a lot to talk about.
Certel公司光缆的破坏
Breach of the Certel fiber-optic cables.
你后备箱里的尸体
Dead body in your trunk.
是啊 是他活该
Yeah, well, he had it coming.
他杀了Henry和其他人
He killed Henry and the others.
你知道 他们可能确实是扑克玩的很烂
You know, they might have been bad poker players,
但是他们不该为此而死
but they did not deserve to die.
别再开玩笑了 这次是认真的
No more jokes. This is serious.
他也想杀我
Well, he tried to kill me, too.
真他妈的走运 我活下来了 没让他得逞
And, dumb luck, I survived and he didn't.
相信我 兄弟 我没有在开玩笑
And trust me, brother, I'm not laughing.
听着 我需要知道真相 Elvis
Look, I need the truth, Elvis.
Warbeck少校有没有因为Certel公司的问题
Did Commander Warbeck come to you for help
向你寻求过帮助 还是因为这件事就是你做的
on the Certel breach or because you were involved?
你觉得我会做那样的事吗
You think I'd do something like that?
你之前做过的 Elvis
You have before, Elvis.
好吧 说得对 说得对 我是做过 但是
Okay, good point, good point, I have, but...
这次我学聪明了 不会再次被抓了
I am too smart to get caught twice.
旋转木马 真的吗
Carousel? Really?
你要当面跟我们说清楚
You got to come in.
那么FBI就可以拿我当替罪羊了
So the FBI could scapegoat me,
就像他们拿你和你的团队当替罪羊一样
like they're scapegoating you and your team.
等一下 Elvis
Wait a minute, Elvis.
你黑进了FBI吗
Did you hack the FBI?
嗨 这是公平的反击
Hey, turnabout's fair play, man.
顺便提醒你一下 哥们 你也是他们的目标
And by the way, you are in their crosshairs, too, brother.
FBI认为你是凶手
FBI thinks that you're a killer.
他们现在就想把你带走
They will not hesitate in taking you out.
因为我是不会进监狱的
They're gonna have to, because I'm not going to prison.
Elvis
Elvis...
Elvis.
回头见 Dwayne
See you around, Dwayne.
他不
He's not...
是我 Christopher
Yeah, Christopher?
我刚从FBI出来
Just got out of the FBI.
我很确信Tammy有了Elvis的线索
Pretty sure Tammy's got a lead on Elvis,
所以我们正在跟踪她
so we're kind of following her.
但是如果你不希望这样 我们可以退出
But we will stand down if you want us to.
不
No.
不 继续跟着 不管发生什么
No, keep on it, whatever happens.
我们必须在FBI找到Elvis之前找到他
We got to get to Elvis before the FBI does.
他不会让FBI活捉他的
He won't let them take him alive.
你一定要小心谨慎 Christopher
You need to be cautious, Christopher.
如果被Tammy发现你在跟踪她
If Tammy realizes what you're doing,
那么一切就都完了
all hell will break loose.
有情况随时跟我汇报
Keep me updated.
听上去情况不是太好
Sounds like you're up to no good.
Lasalle和Sonja正在尾随
Lasalle and Sonja are tailing the FBI agent
调查我们的FBI探员 希望她可以带他们
investigating us, hoping that she will lead them
找到我那在逃的朋友
to my fugitive friend.
真是太糟了
No good at all.
这不算什么
That's nothing.
我试图去证明Certel公司的光纤
Has me trying to confirm that Certel's fiber optics
确实是被人黑进去过
were being hacked.
于是我违反了数十条联邦法律
I'm breaking a dozen federal laws
黑进了Certel公司的光纤
hacking them myself.
FBI根本不在乎Warbeck少校的死
FBI doesn't care about Commander Warbeck's murder.
他们只想知道是否
Only want to prove that there's
真的有什么黑帮阴谋
some sort of a cartel conspiracy.
-为什么不让他们自己折腾呢 -我不能
- Why not let them flounder? - I can't.
这样的代价是 Elvis会被
Odds are, Elvis will get himself killed.
真正的犯罪嫌疑人或是FBI杀掉的
By the actual suspects or the FBI.
你有发现些什么吗 Loretta
You got something, Loretta?
哦 FBI拿走了我们的证据
Oh. The FBI took our evidence, uh,
但是我好像是忘记把Elvis后备箱里
but I may have neglected to give them
那具尸体的照片给他们了
the photos of the body found in Elvis's trunk.
就是Elvis说的那个
The man he said was responsible
谋杀扑克室三人的人吗
for the three murders in the poker room?
此刻我对你充满敬意 Loretta
Brimming with respect for you right now, Loretta.
可我没有时间
Didn't have time
去做适当的尸检
for a proper autopsy,
更没有指纹或DNA
let alone fingerprints or DNA.
但是我有这些
But I have these.
粗糙的 简单墨水印
Crude. Improvised inks.
是 像是在监狱里画的那种
Yeah, something you'd get in prison.
这些刺青表明了他所效力的组织团伙
These tattoos highlight the gangs he ran with.
就像是简历一样
It's like a resume.
Sebastian外出做了些调查 找到了这个人的身份
Sebastian did some legwork, came up with this I.D.
Max Connor
Max Connor.
坐过十年牢
Serving ten years.
抢劫 严重伤害罪
Robbery, aggravated assault.
普通的坏蛋
Common crook.
不是那种能做高级黑客的人
Not the type to get involved in high-level hacking,
更别说是当贩毒集团的雇佣兵
let alone a cartel soldier.
FBI的理论根本讲不通
Blows up the FBI theory.
他必须要有同伙
He had to have had an accomplice.
这个人要精通电脑
Someone with computer skills.
或者是有权限接触到Certel公司的人
Or someone with access to Certel.
好吧 我做些了调查
Uh, well, I-I did a little digging.
结果发现 Max Connor有个兄弟叫James
And turns out, Max Connor has a brother James.
他是Certel公司的技术人员
He's a technician contracted with Certel to run
为他们的水下光缆工作
their underwater cable.
他对工程知识
He had inside knowledge
有很深的了解
of the engineering.
我们这里还有位"神探南茜"啊
Regular Nancy Drew over there.
我想知道他现在在哪
I want to know where he is right now.
马上就找到 我这就打开他手机上的GPS
Way ahead of you. I'm-a pull up the GPS
我们会找到他的
on his phone, we'll find him.
看吧 我告诉过你 你离她太近了
See? I told you, you're getting too close to her.
你什么意思 我离她有两个车的距离
What do you mean? I'm two car lengths behind.
我知道怎么跟踪嫌犯
I know how to follow a suspect.
但她不是嫌犯 她是FBI
Yeah, but she's not a suspect, she's FBI.
如果她发现了我们 我们将失去唯一能找到Elvis的线索
If she makes us, we lose our only lead on Elvis.
也可能失去我们的工作
Probably our jobs.
是的 所以安静点
Yeah, so be quiet.
-哦 是你应该安静点 -相信我
- Oh, you be quiet. - I got this.
真见鬼
Dad-gummit.
啊 我告诉过你的
Ugh, I told you.
-她发现我们了 -她没有
- She made us. - She did not.
好吧 我想我们就在这等着 看她有没有发现
All right, well, I guess we'll just wait here and find out.
嗨
Hey.
好吧 够了
All right, enough.
我们得谈谈了
We got to talk.
不要否认 不要跟我绕弯子
No denials, no deflections.
自从我们在Russo的案子后抱过彼此
You've been acting weird toward me ever since we hugged
你的举止总是怪怪的
after the Russo case.
我们有过那一刻
And... we had a moment.
行了 我要在这里打断你了
Okay, I'm just gonna stop you right there.
因为 是的 我们同意不谈这件事
'Cause we agreed we're not talking about this.
因为我们之间没什么
'Cause we're cool.
因为都是过去的事了
'Cause that's bygones.
我们很不自然
We're anything but cool.
我们应该是一个团队
We're supposed to be a team
互相信任 可是 甚至在我拿水的时候
and trust each other; I can't even reach for my water
你都要把手弹开
without you jumping out of your skin.
我没有弹开
I didn't jump.
我只是 吓了一跳
I was just... startled.
我们是一体的 我们经常会受到攻击
We're a man down and we're under attack, all right?
我们必须彼此靠近 才能支持保护对方
We need to close ranks so that we have each other's back.
我一直很支持你 Lasalle
I've got your back, Lasalle.
我也是
And I got yours.
但是现在
And now...
到底怎么了
What the hell?
哦 拜托
Ooh... boy.
我们完蛋了
Now we are screwed.
好吧
All right.
Pride 我们可能
Yeah, Pride, we might have
会跟FBI发生一点矛盾
a little problem with the FBI.
我们被Gregorio发现了
Gregorio just made us.
该死
Damn.
好吧 她现在在哪儿
Okay, where is she now?
看上去她正走向Rampart
Looks like she's on foot walking down Rampart.
-稍等 -好吧
- Be right with you. - Okay, well,
Patton找到了死去的枪手的兄弟 James Connor
Patton found the brother of our dead gunman, James Connor.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
他可能发现我了
Yeah, he may have spotted me.
对 他发现我了
Yeah, he did.
去Rampart
Headed to Rampart.
Tammy和嫌疑犯都在去那儿的路上
Tammy and the suspect going the same way.
立刻从车里出来
Out of the car, now!
有坏事要发生了
Something's about to go down.
别开枪
Don't shoot me.
-来 走吧 -好吧
- Come on, let's go. - All right.
继续走 表现得自然点
Keep walking. Act natural.
为什么要我在这里和你见面
Why'd you have me meet you here?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
FBI一直在说你坏话 Elvis
FBI are saying bad things about you, Elvis.
说你应该对Henry的死负责
That you're responsible for what happened to Henry.
你了解我的 Anne 我不会伤害Henry
You know me, Anne. I would never hurt Henry.
-我是想帮他 -那你为什么要跑
- I was trying to help him. - So why'd you run?
因为我想自己找出凶手
'Cause I want to figure out who killed him.
但我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
你得给我进入Certel服务器的权限
You have to give me access to Certel servers.
不 我不能帮你
No, I can't give you that.
这是我找到黑客的唯一办法
That's the only way I can find the hacker.
Anne 你得信任我 就像我信任你一样
Anne, you have to trust me as much as I trust you, okay?
Elvis 我真的很抱歉
Elvis, I'm so sorry.
她没给我选择的余地
She didn't give me a choice here.
她
“She”?
把手放在我看得到的地方 Elvis
Hands where I can see them, Elvis.
Anne
Anne...
我手下许多探员就在一个街区之外
I got a dozen agents a block away.
我告诉Anne 在这里我会保持友善
I told Anne here I'd keep it civilized.
-别逼我 -他们在我手机上
- Don't make me a liar! - They had a trace
装了追踪器 他们知道我要来见你
on my phone, they knew I was coming to see you.
别太悲伤了
Don't be too torn apart.
这可能是杀死你男友的凶器
It's probably the weapon that killed your boyfriend.
所有人趴下
Everyone down!
有一个骑摩托的男性嫌疑犯
We got a male suspect on a motorcycle!
我们有个嫌疑犯 James Connor
We got a suspect, James Connor,
朝Esplanade方向 骑着摩托
headed to Esplanade! On a motorcycle!
黑色皮夹克 黑色摩托车
Black leather jacket, black motorcycle.
大伙儿还好吗 Elvis 你没事吧
Everybody all right? Elvis, you okay?
我很好 晚点和你联系
I'm good. I'll call you later.
Elvis 你要去哪儿
Elvis, where the hell are you going?!
你没事吧
You all right?
你个混账 你也跟踪我
You're a jackass! You freakin' follow me, too?!
顺便救了你的命
And saved your life.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你派了人跟踪了
You had people follow an FBI agent
正在调查你们的FBI探员
that's actively investigating you?
你的法医偷藏了尸检的图片
Your M.E. smuggled autopsy photos.
我不清楚你的电脑专家到底干了什么
And I'm not sure what your computer expert did,
但肯定不是好事
but I know that it's not good.
跟你说了 我们不会袖手旁观
Told you we weren't gonna stand down.
不袖手旁观和阻碍公务之间
Well, there's a line between not standing down
是有界限的 不容跨越
and obstruction; and it's not a fine one.
如果不是因为我们 就不会在查Certel的时候
Wasn't for my team, we would not I.D. James Connor
认出James Connor 并阻止他
in the Certel breach, let alone stop him
在这里枪杀Gregorio探员
from shooting Agent Gregorio here.
-这不是关键 -还是挺关键的
- Not the point at all. - It's a little bit the point.
King
King?
有什么发现
What do you got?
我们搜遍了所有地方
We searched the entire area.
在几个街区外发现了James Connor的摩托车
Found James Connor's bike a few blocks away.
没看到他人 但有血迹 他受伤了
Yeah, no sign of him, but there was blood, so he's hurt.
和Patton联络
Hook up with Patton.
找出Connor的最后住址 找到他
Get Connor's last known address. Find him.
抱歉 NCIS正在被审查
Excuse me. NCIS is still under review.
-都不准走 -得了吧 Isler
- No one's going anywhere. - Come on, Isler.
James Connor是我们找到入侵Certel的黑客的唯一线索
James Connor is our only link to whoever hacked Certel.
他不是唯一的线索 我们有Elvis
He's not our only link; we have Elvis.
Elvis差点因为找到黑客而被枪杀
Elvis almost got shot looking for the hacker.
去吧 跟着你的线索走
Go ahead, chase your tail
最后再连累他
trying implicate him as a Ciudad Natal stooge.
我的队伍会继续调查的 去吧
My team will keep working. Go.
你的人哪儿都不准去
Your team stands down.
长官 Pride探员是对的
Sir, Agent Pride is right.
我们最好集中所有资源
Better if we pool our resources,
一起把嫌疑犯缉拿归案
work together to bring the suspects in.
等我们把这案子结了
Plenty of time to escort us to the gallows,
你可以慢慢审查我们
once we've solved the case.
特别探员Gregorio和Butch以及Sundance一起
Special Agent Gregorio, go with Butch and Sundance.
【注：1969年美国电影虎豹小霸王(Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid)中主角】
找到Connor
Find Connor.
你是Butch 我是Sundance
You're Butch, I'm Sundance.
我们扯平了
That makes us even.
Percy和我去前门
Percy and I's got the front.
-你去后门 -为什么我去后门
- You take the back. - Why do I take the back?
-总得有人去 -当然 但那个人不是我
- Someone's got to. - Sure, someone, just not me.
-你在开玩笑么 -你看我在笑么
- Are you kidding me? - Am I smiling?
还真看不出来
Sometimes it's hard to tell.
我的天 我去后门
Geez Louise, I'll take the back.
别开枪打我 行吧
Just don't shoot me, all right?
数到三
On three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
安全
Clear.
It's clear.
安全
Clear.
-Connor跑了 -他不久前还在这儿
- Connor's gone. - He was here recently.
清洗了他的伤口 出城了
Cleaned up his wounds, got out of town?
没带旅行包 应该跑不远
Well, he didn't get far without his “go bag”"
现金 护照 衣服
Cash, passport, clothes.
钱不是问题
Money's not gonna be a problem.
在开曼银行里有存款
Account balances at several Cayman banks.
几百万的存款
Millions of dollars
过去的两周内转进来的
transferred in the last two weeks.
对一个雇佣工而言这是很大一笔钱
That's a lot of dough for a glorified cable guy.
嘿 如果我们错了呢
Hey, what if we're wrong?
如果我们的案子
What if the breach had nothing to do
和间谍行动以及贩毒集团无关呢
with the espionage or the cartels?
如果这只是一场简单的银行抢劫案呢
What if it's just a simple bank robbery?
黑客们和Connor从IDI银行里偷钱
Hackers and the Connors steal the money from the IDI bank
觉得没人能追踪到他们身上
thinking there's no way to trace it.
但当Warbeck发现后 事情败露了
But then things go sideways when Warbeck catches on.
那Connor人呢
Yeah, but where's Connor now?
Elvis 我相信你是无辜的
Elvis, you know I believe you're innocent.
但证据正好相反
But the evidence looks bad.
你自己不解释 我也没法帮你
Got to explain yourself or I can't help.
好吧
Okay.
我能要一碗秋葵吗
Can I get a bowl of gumbo?
听着 我没入侵任何人
Listen, I didn't hack anybody.
Warbeck发现有人入侵Certel
Warbeck found a sniffer down at Certel.
有人把数据从服务器上传了出去
Someone had transferred data off the server.
-什么数据 -Elvis 什么样的数据
- What kind of data? - Elvis, what kind of data?
我不知道 但传到了一家投资银行
I don't know, but it went to an investment bank.
IDI银行
IDI Bank.
因为Ciudad Natal贩毒集团的事情
Under Justice Department investigation
正在被司法部调查
for working with the Ciudad Natal Cartel.
包括其他几千名客户
And about a thousand other clients.
重点是
The point is
Warbeck没法进行追踪 所以我帮了他
Warbeck couldn't trace it, so I helped him out.
-他找了个被判重罪的罪犯帮忙 -他找了位朋友帮忙
- He came to a convicted felon. - He came to a friend.
他想知道到底是外来的攻击
He wondered if it was an attack
还是内部有人在捣鬼
from the outside or an inside job.
他是怎么做的
And how exactly could he do that?
你知道吗 我可以给你解释
You know, I would explain it to you,
但你还是听不懂
but you still would not understand it.
试试看 额
Try and, uh...
解释得简单点吧
Try and dumb it down for me.
Warbeck把损坏的数据给了我
Warbeck brought me the corrupted data.
我检查了所有日志 寻找黑客的蛛丝马迹
I went through the logs looking for the hacker's signature,
因为他们通常会留下一些数据痕迹
because they almost always leave a digital trace.
直接跳到三人打牌被杀的部分
Skip to the part where three men end up dead at the poker game.
我们经常一起打牌
We played poker together all the time.
我在那里是去告诉他们我的发现
I was there to tell them what I'd found.
不幸的是 有人在跟踪我们
Unfortunately, someone was tracking us.
Max Connor 就是死在你后备箱的那个人
Max Connor, who was found dead in your car trunk.
没错 他杀了他们 也想杀死我
Right, he killed those guys, and he tried to kill me, too.
-但我很幸运 -或者他是你的同伙
- And I got lucky. - Or he was your partner,
还有他在Certel工作的兄弟James
along with his brother James, who worked at Certel.
你入侵了服务器 当Warbeck听说此事时
You hacked the servers. When Warbeck got wind of it,
-你就杀了他 -别像个白痴一样
- you had him killed. - Don't be an idiot!
我根本没有做这种事
I had nothing to do with it.
我是在帮我的兄弟 好吗
I was helping out my buddy, okay?
而且我会帮你们找到黑客
And I'll bring you your hacker, all right?
不论他是内部的人 还是外部的人
Whether he's on the inside or the outside.
但你得让我进入Certel的服务器
But you got to let me on Certel's servers.
这样你就能删掉所有证据了吗
So you can clear any damning evidence?
别妄想了 Elvis
Don't hold your breath, Elvis.
愚蠢至极
So stupid.
Dwayne 我向上帝发誓 我说的是事实
Dwayne, I swear to God, I'm telling the truth.
而且我保证字字属实
And I can back up every word of it.
Henry给我的那些文件
Those files that Henry gave me
隐藏在我的笔记本电脑里
are hidden in my laptop.
去查吧
Check it out.
现在 我知道自己搞砸了
Now, I know I'm a screwup,
但是你很清楚
but you know damn well
我和你一样 想找到杀死Henry的凶手
I want to find the killer of Henry just as much as you do.
怎么样
So?
你从文件中发现了什么
What do the files tell you?
Certel的缺口有几百太字节
Hundreds of terabytes of the Certel breach.
主要是IDI银行的数据
IDI Bank mainly.
-和Elvis说的一样 -这证明了
- Just like Elvis said. - All this proves
他有着被盗的数据
is that he had the stolen data.
被盗的数据 还有凶器
That and the murder weapon?
他得马上坐飞机回华盛顿
He's on the next plane back to D.C.
你没有考虑周全
You're not thinking this through.
你还想保护你的朋友吗
You still trying to protect your friend?
这算是新奥尔良的风格吗
Is this some kind of New Orleans thing?
因为我完全不能理解
Because I don't understand it at all.
-看看清楚 -如果我相信Elvis有罪
- Open your eyes. - If I believed Elvis was guilty,
我早就行动了
I'd be leading the charge.
我认为他是替Ciudad Natal做事
I say he's working for Ciudad Natal.
帮助他们暗中破坏我们对他们资金的调查
Helping them to undermine our investigation into their funds.
这只是你的想法 但没有证据证明这是事实
Nothing to prove that except your desire for it to be true.
等我把他带回华盛顿 我会证明的
I'll prove it when I get him back to D.C.
你不了解新奥尔良
You don't understand New Orleans,
但我了解华盛顿 在华盛顿 你的成就
but I understand D.C., and in D.C. you're only as good
只跟你最后的结果有关
as your last accomplishment.
什么意思
There a point?
如果你错了
If you're wrong here--
你确实错了 这就是职业生涯的结束
and you are-- it's career ending.
你会像个傻瓜一样离开
You'll come off like a fool.
你知道我说的没错
You know it's true.
但是
But?
再等12个小时
Wait 12 hours.
让我们的人搜捕James Connor
Let our people track down James Connor.
让Elvis进入Certel
Let Elvis into Certel,
检查他们的服务器
check their servers,
找到真正的黑客
find the real hacker.
-要是他逃跑呢 -他不会的
- And if he runs? - He won't.
我用我的职业生涯做赌注
I'll stake my career on it.
如果他不能证明黑客的存在
And if he can't prove the hacker's still out there,
我会和你一起把他押送到华盛顿
I'll escort him to D.C. with you.
我们在你的手机上安装了无线设备
We got wires hooked into your cell phone.
你能通过耳机听到我们的指示
You'll be able to hear us through this earwig.
另外 我连上了大楼所有的
Plus, I have a feed into the building's
监控摄像头 到处都是我们的眼睛
security cameras. We have eyes all over.
我会注视着你的一举一动
I'll be watching your every move.
反正你们联邦探员
Well, I figure you Feds have been
这么多年一直都在盯着我
doing that for years, anyways.
一旦你不按计划行动
The minute you go off book,
我就立即停止 重新拘捕你
I pull the plug and you're back in custody.
他不会私自行动的
He's not going off book.
嘿 不要私自行动 好吗
Hey, don't go off book, okay?
你过于相信人了
You got a dangerous amount of trust in people.
除此之外 我不知道还有什么方法
I don't know how to do it any other way.
是啊 这次失败的话 咱俩都完蛋
Yeah, this goes wrong, we're both screwed.
你会惹上比我的审查更大的麻烦
You'll have much bigger problems than my review.
什么都不要担心
Don't worry about anything.
只要让我进入服务器
Just get me into the servers.
-我来完成剩下的部分 -Anne
- I'll do the rest. - Anne.
没想到下班了还会在这里见到你
Didn't expect to see you here after hours.
这位是
Who's this?
维护人员
Maintenance.
空调坏了
Problem with the air conditioning.
不能让硬盘的温度太高
Got to keep the hard drives cool.
他们进去了 到现在为止 一切顺利
And they're in. So far, so good.
刚刚发生什么了
What just happened?
不是我们这边的问题
That's not on our end.
有人切断了信号
Someone cut the feed.
在Connor的电脑上有发现
Got something off Connor's computer.
告诉我
Talk to me.
James Connor正在来这儿的路上 如果他还没到的话
James Connor's on his way, if he's not here already.
有人给了他进入Certel的安全密码
Someone gave him the security access code to Certel.
Elvis在哪儿
Where's Elvis?
他在楼上Certel的办公室
He's up in Certel's offices.
监控信号被切断了 很可能是Elvis做的
Security feed got cut, probably by Elvis.
他耍了我们 Pride 他和Connor是一伙的
He played us, Pride. He's working with Connor.
我们现在还不清楚
We don't know anything right now.
你们去找Connor 我去保护Elvis
You find Connor. I'll secure Elvis.
明白
You got it.
我打电话叫支援
I'm calling for backup.
好主意
Good idea.
我可能会惹上大麻烦的
I could get in serious trouble.
FBI派我来的
The FBI sent me here.
你不会有事的
You'll be okay.
记住 我们这么做是为了Henry
Remember, we're doing this for Henry.
James Connor
James Connor!
不许动
Stop where you are!
Connor
Connor!
安全
Clear.
好枪法 女士们
Nice shooting, ladies.
"你浪费太多时间了
"You're taking too long.
我要自己解决"
I'm handling this myself."
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是替Connor做事的人
It means whoever's working
已经进入Certel了
for Connor is already in Certel.
有发现吗
Any luck?
入侵服务器的人
Whoever breached the servers
很好地掩盖了他们的痕迹
did a good job of covering their tracks.
所以 你不能确定黑客的身份
So, you can't I.D. the hacker?
不 我可以
No, no, no, I can,
但这个黑客是从内部入侵的服务器
but the hacker scrubbed the servers from the inside,
所以是Certel的员工
so it was a Certel employee
对这台电脑
with complete security clearance...
有完全的安全权限
from this computer.
你隐藏得很好 Anne
You're very good, Anne.
显然还不够好
Clearly not good enough.
不过你会帮忙的
But you're gonna help.
清除我入侵服务器的所有痕迹
Erase any signs that I hacked the server.
你杀了我的朋友
You killed my friend.
我不会这么轻易删除的
I don't make them too easy.
我不会帮你逃脱的
I'm not gonna help you get away with it.
-你没有选择 -要是我有呢
- You don't have a choice. - Hell if I don't.
Elvis
Elvis!
不要阻止我 Dwayne
Don't try to stop me, Dwayne.
你要想清楚
You need to think this through.
她杀了Henry和另外两个人
She killed Henry and the other two men.
还想毁灭证据
Tried to cover her ass.
我认为她是间谍之类的
Thinks she's some kind of spy or something.
她不是间谍
She's not a spy.
她只是入侵了IDI银行偷钱
She just hacked into the IDI Bank to steal money.
我什么都没做
I didn't do any of it.
Elvis
Elvis...
你知道我的
you know me.
我爱Henry
I loved Henry.
收起你的眼泪和谎言吧
Stop with your tears and your lies,
因为没人会相信它们的 好吗
'cause nobody believes them, okay?!
我发誓 我没想让他受伤
Oh, I swear. I didn't want him to get hurt.
杀他是他们的主意
It was their idea to kill him.
陪审团不会信的
Hard to sell to a jury.
我就是陪审官
I am the jury.
Elvis
Elvis,
你真的需要好好想想
you need to think this through.
扣动扳机 你就毁了自己的生活
Pull that trigger, you're throwing your life away.
Henry值得我伸张正义
Henry deserves justice!
这不是正义 这是报复
This isn't justice. It's revenge.
说辞不同罢了
Those are just words.
不止是说辞
More than that.
让她面对自己的所作所为
Make her face what she's done.
付出代价
Pay the price.
在阴冷的监狱度过余生
Cold cell for the rest of her days.
是她总比是你好
Better her than you.
没有人会进阴冷的监狱
Nobody's gonna spend any time in a cold cell!
这把枪里有很多子弹
There's a lot of bullets in this gun!
不
No.
Henry是我唯一的朋友
Henry was my only friend!
唯一的朋友
Only friend?
你说的对
You're right.
她不值得我这么做
She's not worth it.
Isler副主任
Assistant Director Isler.
让我想想
Let me see.
Anne Foreman被联邦拘留了
Anne Foreman's in federal custody.
Elvis所有的不法行为都会被清除
Elvis is gonna be cleared of all wrongdoing.
我想你来这里 另有他事吧
I'm guessing you're here on some other matter.
嗯
Mm...
虽然我还是不能认同你的方法
I... can't fathom your methods down here,
但令我印象深刻的是
but I'm impressed.
你和你的团队完成了工作
You and your team got the job done.
我们在
Just like we did
John Russo一案中也是如此
in the John Russo case.
好吧 我建议你们
Well, I advise you to follow protocol
下次遇到John Russo这种人 还是按规章办事
next time you come across someone like John Russo,
但我找不到理由责罚你们团队中的任何人
but I see no reason to penalize anyone on your team.
FBI对NCIS的审查结束
The FBI review of NCIS is closed.
好极了
Great.
所以 你也要坐飞机回华盛顿了
So, you're on a plane back to D.C., too.
事实上 非也
Actually, no.
我们没有理由追查NCIS
There's no reason to pursue NCIS,
但仍有证据显示
but there's still evidence
Ciudad Natal在新奥尔良仍然活跃
Ciudad Natal is active in New Orleans.
你们没有财力和
You just don't have the money
硬件技术去对付他们
and the hardware to-to handle them.
我们呆在这里直到他们消失
We stay until they're gone.
哈哈 我能看得出来 你们都吓到了
Well, I can just, I can tell that you're all thrilled.
不如说
Let's just say
我们希望你们尽快把他们清理掉
we look forward to you clearing them out fast.
Pride 我们
Pride, let's, um...
我们私下谈一谈吧
let's talk privately.
好啊
Sure.
Butch. Sundance
Butch. Sundance.
你觉得他是什么意思
What do you think that's about?
不知道 不关心
Don't know. Don't care.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
嘿 Percy
Hey, Percy.
我们还好吗
Are we good?
当然 Lasalle 我们很好
Yes, Lasalle, we're good.
但别再做什么奇怪的事了
Okay, but no more weird stuff.
不再做奇怪的事了
No more weird stuff.
-那些算我的 好吗 -嗯
- Those are on me, okay? - Mm-hmm.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
嘿 Dwayne 我真的很喜欢你的酒吧
Hey, Dwayne, I really like your bar.
这种风格很吸引我隐藏的本性
You know, it's got a style that appeals to my seedier nature.
我应该说声谢谢
Thank you, I think.
音乐很棒
Music is great.
你究竟是怎么做到的
How the hell did you pull that off?
你得认识下Quincy 你的手臂怎么样了
You got to know Quincy. How's your arm?
我都不需要它 这才是我啪啪啪用的手
I don't even need it. This is my lovemaking hand.
什么
What?!
-哇 -嗯
- Whoa! - Huh?
我从没想过我还能看到她
I never thought I'd see her again.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是什么
What's this?
出狱的免费通行证
Get out of jail free card?
工作邀请
Job offer.
你让他们印象深刻 Elvis
You impressed them, Elvis.
FBI网络犯罪部向你敞开了大门
FBI's got an opening in their cyber crime division.
他们需要你这样的人
Could use someone like you.
这意味着重返电脑 并且是合法地
Means getting back on the computer again-- legally.
哇 在"老大哥"的全天候监视下重返电脑
Wow, what an opportunity to be back on a computer
Big Brother：意欲控制人们思想行为的虚伪领导者
这真是一个好机会啊
with Big Brother watching my every move 24/7.
不了 谢谢
No, thank you.
-你看上去并不高兴 -听着 我一生
- You don't seem flattered. - Listen, I worked
都在替"大哥"做事
for “the Man” my whole adult life.
the Man：[俚语]大哥，厉害的人
我要远离网络 兄弟
I am going off the grid, brother,
我不会再回去了
and I ain't coming back.
听着
Listen,
扮演好人不适合我 好吗
playing the good guy ain't for me, okay?
因为代价太大了
'Cause it costs too much.
抱歉打断你 但你一直都是
Sorry to break it to you, but you're always gonna be
好人中的一员 不论你
one of the good guys, no matter how far
有多不愿承认
off the reservation you go.
哦
Oh, boy.
我要迅速开溜了
That's my signal to scram.
-不要惹麻烦 -好的
- Stay out of trouble. - All right.
-你也是 -照顾好自己 兄弟
- You, too, buddy. - Take care, my brother.
-你知道去哪儿找我 -是
- You know where to find me. - Yeah.
我希望我不会去找你
God, I hope don't have to.
不要把你的南部礼仪用在我身上
Don't pull the Southern hospitality on me.
我不渴
I'm not thirsty.
我跟Isler谈过了
Talked to Isler.
他说要我和你的团队一起工作
Said I'm gonna be attached to your team.
只是暂时的
Temporarily.
你帮我们解决案件
You help our cases,
我们帮你解决Ciudad Natal 直到它们瓦解为止
we help you with Ciudad Natal until they're neutralized.
不然的话 我们还会经常碰面的
Otherwise, we're just gonna keep running into each other.
就像你说的 这是个小镇
Like you said, small town.
这是你的主意吗
And this was your idea?
你被留在这里了
You're stuck here.
我是个南方男人
I'm a man down.
你为什么想要我
Why would you even want me?
我曾经调查过你
I was investigating you.
在紧急关头 你站了出来 支持我的意见
When the chips were down, you stepped up, backed my calls.
拜托 我们都想这事快点结束
Come on, we both want this to be over with.
我只是想回家
I just want to go home.
和我们一起工作
Work with us.
我们会帮你揪出贩毒集团
We'll help you ferret out the cartel.
你就可以马上回华盛顿
You'll be back in D.C. in no time.
我也能重新拿回我的城市
I'll get my city back.
双赢
Everybody wins.
为此干杯
I'll drink to that.
========GA字幕组=========
翻译：二噁英  包子  栗子是个男生=_=  Echo  兔子  Lily  草菇
校对：流年  阿珂  大师兄  师太
总校：流年
时间轴&调整：想吃KFC的胖栗子
========GA字幕组=========
=====本集吐槽=====
LaSalle你上来就撩妹
黑人大叔你朝LaSalle吼什么吼！上一个吼LaSalle的大叔是一个CIA探员半集就便当了
这黑客大叔神一般的厉害！偶像！
你们两个为什么要像夫妻一样吵架
果然King更霸气一些
哈哈哈哈，Percy和新探员的争后门简直笑死。还是LaSalle最后去了后门
我的天！最后一句"唯一的朋友"太伤King的心了
新人妹子和黑客大叔都有刷到好感